

# ANDIKA JAYA

DIGITAL MARKETER & JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

+62 236 929 639 ANDIKAJAYAWIGUNA@GMAIL.COM ANDIKAJAYAWIGUNA.GITHUB.IO

### SOCIAL MEDIA









## PROFILE

Experienced Digital Marketer & Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in <strong>Digital Marketing, E-Commerce, and Web Developer Skill, etc. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BIT focused in Computer Science from STIKOM Bali Jimbaran and HELP University.

## EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MARKETER & JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER MINDIMEDIA | 2018 - NOW

### **WEB DEVELOPER**

TECHNOLOGIA CREATIVA | JAN - MAR 2017

# TEAM LEADER & FRONT LINE SALES RATNA BALI HANDPHONE SHOP | 2015 -2017

### EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY, MAJOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

STIKOM BALI (INTERNATIONAL CLASS) | 2014 - 2019 GPA: 3.19

# MARKETING SKILLS

- SEO and Google Analytics
- Social media strategy
- Marketing
- Web content development
- Copywriting

- Corporate blogging
- Project management
- E-Commerce
- Market research

## CODE SKILLS

- PHP
- Javascript
- Laravel
- Ruby on Rails
- GIT

## INTERESTS

**TECHNOLOGY** 

BOOKS

**SPORTS**